[{"answer": " The 1", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "my friend, make a note. We need to schedule more events where somebody gives me a really big fish", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "After the elections", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "We can't take it out for a spin, my friend. We need it to get r", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Well... you play it with gusto", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Are they supposed to be", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " What did you mean when you said you don't have a phone", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " How did I get the number. That's a reasonable question. I don't know. Probably the that place", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "We should have gone after the handguns", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "We don't have time to do one thing at a time", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Very funny.  Really, where did you learn", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Sweetie, did Mom teach you how to do this", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You know, I'm a little nervous", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Be myself", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Be myself", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Her shoes", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I'll take care of it, sir. Where do you want them sent", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I don't understand", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I don't understand", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You just want the phone number", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What is it...what is it", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " A ham", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " Thanks for seeing me on such short notice", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I got the ham, yes. Thank you very much", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Either one. I have to be in and out", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend wants to talk about grazing rights. Trust me", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Sorry. You have concerns", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Does it having anything to do with one of us being the President", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "The dentist", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You've got a shor", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "It was nice meeting you, Mrs", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "It was nice meeting you, that place", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "that place", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Thank you. It was nice meeting you", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": ":  I think this is the dish room", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Yeah, it is. It's the room with all the dishes", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "It's the that place Room", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "There're about seve", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Do you think there will ever come a time when you can stand in a room with me and not think of me as the President", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I got news for you, that place. As a lobbyist, you would never be alone in a room with the President", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Libyan I.H.Q's in the middle of downtown that place", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Are we gonna miss", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I think it's a great idea, sir. You know that place's gonna be talking about your lack of military service", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "But it can be, sir. What you did tonight was very presidential", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "There's nothing that needs prepping. A.J., let's meet with the leadership after we meet with the that place", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Nobody gets ten minutes today", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": " Where in the White House?", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "The dish room", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "What's my problem", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Sex and nervousness is my problem", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Who? Who's camped out", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "The press is camped out", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Thank God", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "See, and I think the important thing is actually not to be panicking", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Well, if we're gonna try, we should do some prep work. You wanna order in", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Okay. I'm having lunch at the that place, so we'll have to, you know, start real early..", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "my friend sees it as a problem. I see it as a opportunity", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "We caught it", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Let me see if I've got thi", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Don't deal with it", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Now?", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "It's not what men do. I know no men who do that", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": " What about yours", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": " I've got some work I was gonna bring home. Why", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": " The negotiations are going pretty well here. It looks like the nation's going to keep on flying. my friend's sleeping over at a friend's house Saturday night", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": " Have you ever been to Camp my friend", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": " I'm not sayin", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": " I'm not making an ac", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "I have one more election left, that place. I don't have the luxury of losing my patience", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Things will be better when I pass a crime bill. And that place, if you disappeared, I'd find you", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "It was a disaster", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "Well, congratulations, fellas, you're outta the cellar. my friend told me the only thing on the President's domestic agenda they were more committed to defeating than the crime bill was the fossil fuel package", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "It doesn't change the facts, Mr. President. If that place gets her 24 votes and we're three short, there's some maneuvering to be done", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "You made a deal, Mr. President", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "I made a promise, A.J", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "I made it with that place", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "You made a deal, Mr. President", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "You made it with the that place", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": " How're the numbers", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "How bad", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "What's in that place", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "When did you decide to get a new job", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "If my friend hadn't died...would we have won three years ago", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "If we'd had to go through a character debate three years ago, would we have won", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": " How are you doing in your Constitutional debates", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "You're done", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "my friend, call the printer", "docId": "American-President_-The.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "Every word, my friend. It's a whole new ball game. You've got 35 minutes", "qsentId": 88}]